Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Fiscal Sponsorship, 1971-2011; 52 linear feet in 52 record cartons
  - Subseries C. Artists' Projects, 1982-2011; 36 linear feet in 36 record cartons
    - Zhang, Ruth, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 77)
    - Zhu, Ying Ying, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 78)
    - Zanichkowsky, Stephen, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 79)
    - Kreitzer, Carson, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Series VIII. Other NYFA Programs, 1970-2010; 45 linear feet in 45 record cartons
  - Subseries A. Arts in Education, 8 linear feet
    This subseries consists of program and development information through correspondence, memorandum, and research notes for Arts in Education; Technical Assistance Program (TAP) application forms and panelists' recommendation forms; Artists in the School Community applications forms and panelists' recommendation forms; Artists and Teachers Partnership for Excellence Multiple Intelligences Project post- and pre-tests forms, including teacher comments and state education department information for schools under registration review (SED-SURR); Design Education Initiative resources, which include external information from various institutions in collaboration NYFA utilized to create the program; and correspondence and memorandum for the New York City Music Initiative, creating a timeline of the program.
    The subseries is arranged based on the programs under Arts in Education, as mentioned in the scope and content note. TAP and Artists in the School Community applications are alphabetically and chronologically arranged. Multiple Intelligences Project, Design Education Initiative Resources, and New York City Music Initiative materials are arranged chronologically.
    Historical Note
    The Arts in Education (AIE) program was funded by the New York City Department of Education under the New York Foundation for the Arts.
    - Education Department Summary, 1998-99, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Education Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Education Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Education Programs, 1999-2000, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Information and Research 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Information and Research 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Information and Research 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Public Programs Department, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Information and Research 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Public Programs Department, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Public Programs Department, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Public Programs Department, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - General Files, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - General Files, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - General Files, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General Files, Rosters, Correspoondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Promotional Material, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - New York Council for the Humanities, General Files, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - New York Council on the Humanities, General Files, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - New York Coalition for the Humanities, General Files, Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - General Files, Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - General Files, Correspondence, Memorandums, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - General Files, Correspondence, Promotional Material, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - General Files, Correspondence, Promotional Material, Memorandum, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - General Files, Correspondence, Promotional Material, Press, Memorandum, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - General Files, Correspondence, Promotional Material, Press Releases, Memoranda, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - General Files, Art Start, Correspondence, Memoranda, Press, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - General Files, Correspondence, Finance, Memos, Press, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - General Files, New York Council of the Humanities, Correspondence, Memoranda, Press, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - General Files, Press Releases, Newspaper Articles, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - General Files, Press Releases, Newspaper/Magazine Articles, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - General Files, Research, The Cummington School, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - General Files, Research, Correspondence, Press, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - General Research Files, "Strengthening the Vital Link.. .", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - General Research Files, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - NYFA Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Common Ground Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Common Ground, Trends and Visions, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - The Center for Arts Education Implementation Grant (NYFA Partnership), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Common Ground, Annual Conference for Arts Educators and Arts Professionals, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - FYI: Cultural Diversity of Arts and Cultural Organizations, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - AIR (Formerly Artists-in-Schools) Application/Proposal, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Common Ground, Annual Conference for Arts Educators and Arts Professionals, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Annual Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Common Ground, Annual Conference for Arts Educators and Arts Professionals, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Common Ground, Artists-in-Residence Project Residency Resource Packet, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - The Center for Arts Education Planning Grant (NYFA Partnership), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ArtsConnection, "Dance" A Social Study," by Elizabeth Zimmer and Mindy Levine, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ArtsConnection, "Dance" A Social Study," by Elizabeth Zimmer and Mindy Levine, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Doing Art Together", 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - ArtsPartners Application, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Request for Proposal, National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Funding Report, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Funding Report, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Funding Report, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Funding Report, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Funding Report, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Funding Report, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Program Guidelines FY 1988-1989, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Application Guidelines, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "New York: The State of the Arts, Issues and Ideas", 1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Arts Education for the 21st Century American Economy, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Visual Artists Program, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Teachers and Writers Collaborative Program Literature Residency, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Teachers and Writers Collaborative Program Literature Residency, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - New York City Arts in Education Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Museums Collaborative School Program, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Greg McCaslin, Equal Employment Opportunity Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Greg McCaslin, NYFA Developmental Forms, Budgets, and Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Greg McCaslin, ArtsWire: Online Communications for the Arts, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Original Forms, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - TAP Consultants, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Final Report Summaries for TAP Sites, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Consultants Evaluation meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - AIE Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Forms, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - AIE Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Revisions, Forms, Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Artist and Scholar Residence Project, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Abbott Union Free School District, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Albion Central School, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - American Folk Theater, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Ananda Dancers, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Arts Council of Rockland, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - ArtsPartners, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bronx Creative Arts for Youth, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Broome County Arts Council, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - GGNW Adult Learning Center, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Children's Art Carnival, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chango Elementary School, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Copake-Taconcic Hills Central SD, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Council for the Arts in Westchester, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Doing Art Together, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Dutchess County Arts Council, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Everson Museum of Art, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Franklin Furnace, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Il Piccolo Teatro Dell'Opera, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Lakeland Central School District, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Literary Education Organization Consortium, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Media Alliance, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - NYC Alternative High Schools, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Northern Westchester Center for the Arts, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Oswego County BOCES, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Penfield Central Schools, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Pregnant Teens Program - NYC Board of Education, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Robert Blackburn's Printmaking Workshop, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Syracuse Opera, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Touchstone Center for Children, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Tri-Cities Opera, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Vanaver Caravan, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Woodside on the Move, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Wayland Central School Districts, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Overview/Participant Abstracts, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Broadhollow Players, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Center for Safety in the Arts, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - CSD #01/PS 140, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - CSD #03/Waldeigh Alternative Arts Middle School, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - CSD #28/PS 99, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Community Works, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Genesee Center for Arts, Education and New Ideas, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - MacCormick Secure Center, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Mount Sinai: Medical Center Through Our Eyes Productions, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Narrowsburg Central School District, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - New Orchestra of Westchester, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Pearl River Union Free School Disctrict, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - The Phoenix Ensemble, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Putnam Arts Council, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Rejoicensemble!, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Rockland Center for the Arts, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Theatre in Motion, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Tukahoe High School, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Ulster County BOCES, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Wallkill Central School District, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Washington, Warren, Hamilton, Essex BOCES, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Wayne-Finger Lakes BOCES, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Artists With Class, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Broadway Theater Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Bronx Council on the Arts, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Community Works, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Creative Time, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - CSD #13/PS 8, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - "SHEAC" School Heart Environmental Art Community, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dream Yard Drama Project, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Essex Community Heritage Organization, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - The Jay Heritage Center, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Marquis Studios, Ltd., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - New Perspectives Theatre Company, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Northern Westchester Center for the Arts, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Rennselaer County Council for the Arts, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Starfish Theatreworks, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Ulster BOCES, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Walkill CSD/Ostrander Elementary School, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Westchester Arts Council, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Westchester Philharmonic, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Young Audiences of Rochester/#1 Monroe BOCES, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Chronology, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Technical Assistance Program (TAP) Chronology, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Arts in Education Institute, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Bloomingdale School of Music, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Chekhov Theatre Ensemble, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Community Music Project, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - District 75/Office of Arts Education, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Go Figure! Outreach Program, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Hangar Theatre, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Hoosick Falls, Renseller County, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Hudson Valley Shakespeare Festival, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Ithaca City School District, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Lotus Fine Arts Productions, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - New York State School for the Blind, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - New York Youth Symphony, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - New York Youth Symphony, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Newark Central Schools, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - PS 183 NYC, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Red Creek High School, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Red Creek District Arts Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Remington School, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Sherburne-Earlville Elementary School, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Spanish Dance Arts Company, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - StageWorks on the Hudson, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Alterative High School/International HS, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Bard College, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Basis Curtis High School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - CSD #01/PS 137, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - CSD #02/Institute of Collaborative Education, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - CSD #10/PS 33/Timothy Dwight Elementary School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - CSD #15/Brooklyn School for Global Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CSD #22/PS 139/Alexine A. Fenty School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - CSD #75/PS 224Q, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - CSD #75/PS 721/Richard H. Hungerford School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - CSD #75/PS 752Q/Queens School for Career Development, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Albany City School District/Philip Livingston Magnet Academy, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Albany PS 19, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Arts in Education Institute, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Blue Rock School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Bolton Central School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Children's Media Project, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Circuit Productions, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - CSD #72/PS 425X/Evander Childs High School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - CSD #31/PS 13, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - CSD #31/PS 23, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Erie 1 BOCES, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Glen Falls Symphony Orchestra, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Geneva City Schools/North Street Elementary School and West Side Elementary School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Holland Central School District, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Mont Pleasant Middle School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Pavilion Central School/Dorothy B. Bunch Elementary School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Pine Grove Elementary School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - PS 261 Magnet School for Integrating the Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Schenectady City School District/King Magnet School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Second Opportunity Schools, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Syracuse City School District/Franklin Magnet School of Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Syracuse Diocese/St. Peter's School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Syracuse University Early Childhood Education and Day Care Center, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Syracuse University Early Childhood Education and Day Care Center, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Sullivan County BOCES, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Sidney Center Elementary School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Taconic Hills Central School Districts, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Townsend Harris High School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - The Union Free School District of the Tarrytowns/Tappan Hill School, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Upstate Homes for Children and Adults, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Proposal to to State Education Department (SED), 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Financials, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Schedule of Activities, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Project Overview, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Contract, Statement of Work, and Project Evaluation, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - CS 44 Post-Tests and Teacher Instructions, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - PS 66 Post Tests and Teacher Instructions, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - CS 44 Teacher Evaluations, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - PS 66 Teacher Evaluations, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Participants and Collaborators, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Prospective Mentors, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Prospective Artists, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Prospective Artists, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Evaluation Plan and Forms, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Prospective Schools for Orientation, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Workshop I (January 6 and 7), 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Design Education Initiative Formative Meetings, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Design Initiative as of 11/96, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Design Education Initiative Proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Design Education Initiative Timeline, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Criteria for Assessing Models of Learning through Design, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Design Education Initiative Advisory Meeting, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Web Site Evaluations, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Website Developments, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - DataBase lists, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Design Education Initiative Workshops, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - The American Architectural Foundation, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - American Planning Association, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Architecture Resource Center, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Bard Graduate Center, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Blue Marble, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Brooklyn Center for the Urban Environment, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Burchfield-Penney Art Center, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Center for Environment, Education and Design Studies, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Center for Understanding the Build Environment, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - City-As-School High School, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Crizmac Art and Cultural Education Materials, Inc., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Design Arts and the Public Agenda (DADA), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Design Museum - UK, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Education by Design (EDB), Antioch New England Graduate School, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - El Puente, Academy for Peace and Justice, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - The Eli Whitney Museum, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Friends of the Upper East Side, Historic Districts, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Henry Street Settlement, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Historic Districts Council, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Idater, Department of Design and Technology at Loughborough University, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - International Technology Education Association (ITEA), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Learning and Leadership in Families, Inc., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Learning By Design, NY, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - National Buidling Museum, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - National Society for Education in Arts and Design, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - People Learning About City Environments (PLACE) Network, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Pratt Institute Center for Community and Environmental Development (PICCED) (1/2), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Pratt Institute Center for Community and Environmental Development (PICCED) (2/2), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Queens Museum of Art, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Reading-Fleming Middle School, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Salvadori Educational Center on the Built Environment, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Technology, Humanities, and the Environment (THE) Option, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Ties Magazines, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - University of the Arts Philadelphia - DK 12, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - UK City of Architecture and Design, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - University of the Arts, Philadelphia, National Design for Thinking Institute, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Ventures in Education, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Ventures in Education, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Ventures in Education, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Young Audiences of New Jersey, Inc., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Worldstudio Foundation, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The New York City Choral Music Initiative Chronology, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)